<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi! Gaurav here on Gaurav Kamble</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi! Gaurav here on Gaurav Kamble</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project I : Tesla Stock Price Prediction</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Tesla Stock Price Prediction     Referred the Tesla Stock Price dataset from Kaggle.
  Used the feature which included the Closing Stock Prices from the dataset.
  Built a Recurrent Neural Network model using LSTM to forecast the future Stock Prices of the Company.
  Trained the DL model on 1117 records and tested it on 575 records.
  Achieved :
 Training RMSE = 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project II: Face Mask Detection</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Face Mask Detection     Referred the Face Mask Detection datasaet from Kaggle
  Built a CNN model with Transfer Learning using the convolutional layers of the VGG16 model
  Generated extra data from the existing dataset by using Data Augmentation
  Trained the CNN model on 10,000 images, validated it upon 800 images and tested the model on 992 images
  Achieved :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project III : Cardiovascular Disease Prediction</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Cardiovascular Disease Prediction     Referred the Cardiovascular Disease dataset from Kaggle
  Built an ANN model to predict whether a person is wearing a mask or not
  Performed EDA and handled outliers present within the dataset
  Used Keras Tuner to optimize the hyperparameters of the ANN model
  Achieved :
 Training Accuracy = 99 % Testing Accuracy = 83 %    GitHub Link of the Project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project IV : Dissolved Oxygen Level in River Water</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Dissolved Oxygen Level in River Water     Referred the Dissolved Oxygen Level in River Water dataset from Kaggle
  The dataset contained 37 no. of features, and many of them included NaN values
  Dropped the features containing more than 60% of NaN values, and replaced the NaN values with the mean value of that feature for the important features
  Performed EDA and handled outliers present within the dataset</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project V : University Salaries Prediction</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>University Salaries Prediction     Referred the University Salaries dataset from Kaggle which included the base pay of the Professors from the University of Vermount(UVM) from 2009 to 2021
  The dataset contained 14470 records including no missing values
  Performed EDA and found out that there are no outliers present within the dataset
  Solved the problem using standard procedure as well as by using sklearn Pipeline</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can get in touch with me here
   Platform URL     E-mail : gauravkamble9@gmail.com   LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/gaurav-kamble-aa02011b3/   Github : https://github.com/GauravK1997    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
